Guide to the United Automobile Workers of America, District 65 Records WAG 006
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VII: Shop Files, 1937-1971 (Box 68 - 154)
  - HY-KL
    - Hyklass Food Products, 1947-1961 (Box 150, Folder 2-3)
    - Hyman Hefland, 1945-1948 (Box 150, Folder 4)
    - L. Hyman Co., 1940-1950 (Box 150, Folder 5)
    - Hyman & Hyman Beauty Products Inc., 1940-1950 (Box 150, Folder 6)
    - IPCO Hospital Supply Corp., 1965-1966 (Box 150, Folder 7)
    - I.W.O., 1950-1952 (Box 150, Folder 8)
    - Independent News Co., Inc., 1959-1961 (Box 150, Folder 9)
    - International Container, 1951 (Box 150, Folder 10)
    - Interscience Publishers, 1949 (Box 150, Folder 11)
    - Ippolito, 1947-1957 (Box 150, Folder 12)
    - Israel Speaks, 1950-1952 (Box 150, Folder 13)
    - Irwill Knitting Co., 1941 (Box 150, Folder 14)
    - Joseph Jacobs, 1937-1948 (Box 150, Folder 15)
    - William Jelling, 1941-1951 (Box 150, Folder 16)
    - Jewel Trend, 1942-1950 (Box 150, Folder 17)
    - Joseph Julie Co., 1939-1946 (Box 150, Folder 18)
    - Journeyman Tailors Union, 1951 (Box 150, Folder 19)
    - Kandell, Inc., 1947-1949 (Box 150, Folder 20)
    - Harry Katias, 1938-1945 (Box 150, Folder 21)
    - R.O. Kent Co., 1950-1952 (Box 150, Folder 22)
    - Kitty Kelly Footwear, 1946-1949 (Box 150, Folder 23)
    - Klarks Klothes, 1949-1951 (Box 150, Folder 24)
    - Klein Bros. Fabric Corp., 1943-1951 (Box 150, Folder 25)
  - KN-N
    - Knickerbocker Textile Corp., 1940-1949 (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - A. Lambort Bros., 1943-1949 (Box 151, Folder 2)
    - Lambert Novelty Mirror Works, 1947-1948 (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - Lancedale Knitting, 1963-1964 (Box 151, Folder 4)
    - Laufer & Rothbaum, Inc., 1949, 1951 (Box 151, Folder 5)
    - Leart Products, 1946-1948 (Box 151, Folder 6-8)
    - Levy Bros. China Co., 1947-1953 (Box 151, Folder 9)
    - Lewis & Sons Master Watchmakers, Inc., 1947-1950 (Box 151, Folder 10)
    - Liberty Book Club, 1949 (Box 151, Folder 11)
    - Liberty Corrugated Container Corp., 1948-1960 (Box 151, Folder 12-13)
    - Lieb Cigar, 1945-1952 (Box 151, Folder 14)
    - Lignum Chemical Works, 1942-1950 (Box 151, Folder 15)
    - Lincoln & Ulmer, 1946-1950 (Box 151, Folder 16)
    - Lion Gene Textile, 1946, 1954 (Box 151, Folder 17)
    - R. Littman Doughnut Corp., 1950 (Box 151, Folder 18)
    - Retail Merchants Advisory Council, Inc., 1953 (Box 151, Folder 19)
    - Millinery Hat Jobbers Ready to Wear, 1943 (Box 151, Folder 20)
    - NYMCO (company exhibits), 1947 (Box 151, Folder 21)
    - NYMCO (Sam Eisenstadt discharge), 1950 (Box 151, Folder 22)
    - Namms Inc., 1940-1949 (Box 151, Folder 23)
    - National Desertion Bureau, 1948-1949 (Box 151, Folder 24)
    - Navarro & Gonzalez, 1945-1951 (Box 151, Folder 25)
    - New American Library, 1947-1959 (Box 151, Folder 26)
    - N.Y. Assoc. of Wholesalers of Ladies & Kids Hats, 1942-1943 (Box 151, Folder 27)
    - New York Cigar co., 1947-1960 (Box 151, Folder 28)
    - Newark Social Service, 1951-1952 (Box 151, Folder 29)
    - Newspaper Guild, 1948 (Box 151, Folder 30)
    - Newspaper Guild of New York, 1946-1948 (Box 151, Folder 31)
  - O-PO
    - Joseph Obergh, 1940-1958 (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - Odora Co., Inc., 1945-1951 (Box 152, Folder 2)
    - Oxford Book, 1949-1951 (Box 152, Folder 3)
    - S.T. Paley, 1940-1948 (Box 152, Folder 4)
    - Palizzio, 1948-1951 (Box 152, Folder 5)
    - Parfum L'Orle, Inc., 1940-1948 (Box 152, Folder 6)
    - Parcels to Russia, Inc., 1941 (Box 152, Folder 7)
    - Paris Cosmetics, 1947 (Box 152, Folder 8)
    - Edward P. Paul & Co., Inc., 1940-1941 (Box 152, Folder 9)
    - Pedigree Fabrics, Inc., 1941-1943 (Box 152, Folder 10)
    - Peerless Art Co., Inc., 1945-1946 (Box 152, Folder 11)
    - S.B. Penick & Co., 1941-1943 (Box 152, Folder 12-14)
    - J.C. Penny Co., 1946-1948 (Box 152, Folder 15-17)
    - Perfect Shoulder Pad Co., 1940-1941 (Box 152, Folder 18)
    - Chas Pfizer, 1946 (Box 152, Folder 19)
    - Philco Service, Inc., 1949 (Box 152, Folder 20)
    - Philippine Embroidery Corp., 1941 (Box 152, Folder 21)
    - Pioneer Refolding Co., 1947 (Box 152, Folder 22)
    - Plastic Novelties Inc., 1941 (Box 152, Folder 23)
    - Plastic Utilities Mfg. Co., 1946-1947 (Box 152, Folder 24)
    - Plastic Ware Inc., 1950 (Box 152, Folder 25)
    - Plastiglas Printing, 1947 (Box 152, Folder 26-31)
    - Plymouth Shops, 1940-1948 (Box 152, Folder 32-34)
    - Polizzio, Inc., 1946 (Box 152, Folder 35)
    - Porcelain Metals Inc., 1941 (Box 152, Folder 36-37)
    - Portofonic Mfg. Corp., 1947-1948 (Box 152, Folder 38)
    - Dr. Posner Shoe, 1940-1947 (Box 152, Folder 39)
    - Powell & Campbell, 1941-1947 (Box 152, Folder 40)
  - PR-STE
    - Premier Co., 1941-1948 (Box 153, Folder 1)
    - Premier Engraving, 1941-1942 (Box 153, Folder 2)
    - Premo Lab, 1941-1943 (Box 153, Folder 3-5)
    - Pressner & Co., 1938-1941 (Box 153, Folder 6)
    - Prevue Television Service Inc., 1950 (Box 153, Folder 7)
    - Price Theatre Premium, 1941-1942 (Box 153, Folder 8)
    - Princeton Shoe, 1944-1947 (Box 153, Folder 9)
    - Princeton Silk, 1940-1941 (Box 153, Folder 10)
    - Progress Burlap Bag Co., 1941-1942 (Box 153, Folder 11)
    - Progressive Tool Works, 1942-1945 (Box 153, Folder 12)
    - Prowler & Samuels, 1941-1942 (Box 153, Folder 13)
    - Publix Metal, 1942-1947 (Box 153, Folder 14)
    - Puritan Woolen, 1946-1956 (Box 153, Folder 15)
    - Purity Drug Co., 1946 (Box 153, Folder 16)
    - John G. Purs, 1941 (Box 153, Folder 17)
    - Quality Pearl, 1947-1950 (Box 153, Folder 18)
    - Quiltex Mfg. Co., 1958 (Box 153, Folder 19)
    - Radio (unorganized), 1946 (Box 153, Folder 20)
    - Rafael Rodriquez, 1946-1960 (Box 153, Folder 21)
    - Readers Scope, 1946-1948 (Box 153, Folder 22)
    - E. Regensburg & Sons, 1946-1947 (Box 153, Folder 23)
    - Renart Sportswear, 1941-1949 (Box 153, Folder 24)
    - Robert Hall, 1946 (Box 153, Folder 25-26)
    - Royal Corrugated Box Co., 1947-1948 (Box 153, Folder 27)
    - Schranze & Bieger Co., Inc., 1946 (Box 153, Folder 28)
    - William R. Scott, 1948 (Box 153, Folder 29)
    - Sewing Economy Inc., 1950-1951 (Box 153, Folder 30)
    - Sheffield Mfg. Co., 1947 (Box 153, Folder 31-32)
    - Slatter Robbins Co., 1953-1954 (Box 153, Folder 33)
    - Spangle Novelty Co., 1946 (Box 153, Folder 34)
    - Standard Appliance, 1949 (Box 153, Folder 35)
    - Stern & Stern, 1939-1961 (Box 153, Folder 36)
    - Stewarts Cafeterias, 1946-1953 (Box 153, Folder 37)
  - STI-Z
    - Still-man Co., 1946-1947 (Box 154, Folder 1)
    - Strike Preparation for 65, 1948 (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - So-Rite Fashions, 1949 (Box 154, Folder 3)
    - Tanbro Fabrics Corp., 1949-1951 (Box 154, Folder 4)
    - Taub Dental Labs, 1942 (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - Textile Associates, 1940-1960 (Box 154, Folder 6)
    - Tri-Camp, 1949 (Box 154, Folder 7)
    - Unicorn Press, Inc., 1949 (Box 154, Folder 8)
    - United States Packaging Corp., 1956 (Box 154, Folder 9)
    - Uptown Convertibles Assoc., Inc., 1946 (Box 154, Folder 10)
    - Utility Quilting & Binding Co., 1942 (Box 154, Folder 11)
    - U.S. Instrument Co., 1944 (Box 154, Folder 12)
    - Vanguard Press, 1947 (Box 154, Folder 13)
    - Vatco Label Corp., 1948-1953 (Box 154, Folder 14-15)
    - Veterans of Abraham Lincoln, 1950 (Box 154, Folder 16)
    - Victory Sample, 1947 (Box 154, Folder 17)
    - Vitagraph Studios, 1942 (Box 154, Folder 18)
    - Vogue Industry & Vogue Optical, 1946 (Box 154, Folder 19)
    - Phillip Wilcox, 1947 (Box 154, Folder 20)
    - Willesden, 1943-1944 (Box 154, Folder 21)
    - Winthrop Mfg. Co., 1959 (Box 154, Folder 22)
    - Wishnetsky Food Products Wholesale Hardware Union, 1940-1941 (Box 154, Folder 23)
    - Wholesale Hardware Union, undated (Box 154, Folder 24)
    - Z-K Equipment Co., 1943-1944 (Box 154, Folder 25)
    - Zell Products Corp., 1941-1945 (Box 154, Folder 26-39)
    - Zylite Optical, 1942-1947 (Box 154, Folder 40-42)
- Series VIII: Officers' Files, 1933-1992. Eventually this series will includes material from the unprocessed portion of the collection (notably the David Livingston files). One portion of this series (17 linear feet) has been separated and processed as the Papers of Cleveland Robinson (Wagner 6.1).
- Series IX: Unprocessed Material, 1933-1995.
  - Subseries IX:A: General Files, 1959-1995
    - Survey of unorganized shops Bound in 5 portfolios, undated (Box 154A)
    - Organizing Campaigns: Boston University/UMass, Columbia University, 1980s-1991 (Box 155)
    - Organizing Campaigns: Columbia University, Prentice-Hall, Harper & Row, 1980s (Box 156)
    - Organizing Campaigns: Hartz Mountain, La Salle Committee, Air Express International, ADEMCO, Archives, Association of Graduate Student Employees, 1980s-1990s (Box 157)
    - Organizing: Garment locals, Jewish Affairs, undated (Box 158)
    - Correspondence, Region 9-A: Resolutions, Reports, E.W. Barrett, John J. Flynn, 1980s (Box 159)
    - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, 1965-1980 (Box 160)
    - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, 1980-1989 (Box 161)
    - Political Action, 1980s-1991 (Box 162)
    - Retirees: Bed-Stuy, Canarsie, Flushing, Harlem, 1989-1991 (Box 163)
    - Retirees: Southern Brooklyn, Ethnic Day, Jamaica, Northeast Bronx Community Group, undated (Box 164)
    - (Document Box) Retirees: Flushing, Western Queens, Widow/Widower Support Group, undated (Box 165)
    - New Jersey General Council Minutes (4 portfolios); The 65 Security Plan Board of Trustees Meeting, 1974-1984 (Box 166)
    - Miscellaneous Files: Dist. Atty. Silver, Martin E. Segal Co., Security Plan Memos, Seafarers Int'l Union, RWDSU, Right to Work Campaign, Rosanna Knit, Lord Bertrand Russell art. on Russia, Reach-Out Retirees Program, Joe Pamerlen, Political Affairs, Police Dept., undated (Box 167)
    - Miscellaneous Files: Labor Day 1961, 1963, 1968; New Applicants 1959; Teacher Info: Textbooks; Strike Materials; Unorganized Shop Surveys (unprocessed); Social Service Employees Union, 1981; South Bronx Revitalization Program, 1979; Speech, Henry Foner introducing Abe Feinglass, 1979; Garment Center Strike, May 1, 1973, undated, 1959-1982 (Box 168)
    - Miscellaneous Files (Education, Political Action, Strike Support): Arthur Osman Scholarship, Education Bulletin, Labor Day 1984-1989, Brooklyn Legal Service, Columbia Strike-1984, Columbia Organizing-1984-85, Hermans Contract, Colt Firearms, Dist 65 Constitution & Bylaws, "Womens Stuff", Model Contract, Health & Safety, Nelson Mandela, undated, 1984-1989 (Box 169)
    - Inventories: (Document Box) 3 portfolios, 1973-1992 (Box 170)
  - Subseries IX:B: Legal Department, 1963-1967
    - Tru-Art Print Corp., Govs Comm. on the Minimum Wage-Nov 1964, NLRB Proceedings-Dist 65v.Weil Ceramics & Glass-Jul 1965, People v. Gilberto Gerena-1965-1966, People v. Thaddeus Jawerski & Thomas Vinella-1965, Winthrop Mfg. Co & Foursome Windows, Wholesale Laundry Board of Trade, Bob Willis, Woolen Jobbers Assoc/Strand Woolen Corp., Young, Nocito and Colabro, Zagan, Julius (Bell Textile Corp.), Arbitration: Dist 65 v. Columbia Combing Corp.-Mar 1965, DCA Food Industries INC. v. David Livingston-1965, NLRB Proceedings-Darmon Tool Co.-Mar 1965, David Livingston v. Empire Textile Corp.-Apr-May 1965, undated, 1964-1966 (Box 171)
    - H. Greenwald Mfg. Co.-Aug 1966, Mucon Corp-Jan-Jun 1965, Trenton Malt Bev. Corp/F.A. Bamman Inc.-1963-1967, Unemployment Ins. & Retirement Pay, Unfair Labor Practice Charges, United Artists Pension Plan Arbitration, Universal Screw & Bolt Co., The Upjohn Co., Gilberto Genera Valentin, Valiant Radio, Valtex Fabrics, Varitex Corp., Venice Knitting Mills Inc., VIM Welfare Assoc. Harry M. Wagner Co. Inc., Henry Warheit-Arbitration, Wearbest Silk Mills Inc., Weatherall Products Inc., Marie Welch, Weil Ceramics & Glass Inc., Dr. A.B. Weinstein, E. Weinstein Inc., Sol Westheimer Co. Inc. (Dimas e Cortes), undated, 1963-1967 (Box 172)
    - St. Johns University Matter, Samuel Sachs & Co., Louis Schaeffer Inc., Schiffli Lace & Embroidery Mfg. Assn. Inc., Schranz & Bieber Co. Inc., Monroe Schutz Co. Inc., Alma Schwartz Unemployment Ins. (A. Cohen & Son), Schwatz Chemical Co., Schwartz, Mrs. Martha (Security Plan), Security Plan Arbitrations, Security Plan Collections, The 65 Security Plan, Lou Seidman & Sons (Robert & Edward Seidman), Seligman & Iatz Inc. (Gertz-Hicksville), Seneca Quilting Co. Inc., Sheridan Creations, Henry I. Siegel Co. Inc., Simon, Healy & Goldstein, Sklar & Rosenshein, Square Deal Stationary & Toy Inc., Standard Refrence Publishing Co. Inc., Star Notions Co. Inc., Paul A. Straub Co. Inc., The Studio Guild Inc., Herman Sukon Co. Inc., Sy-Mar Notions Co., The Tablet & Ticket Co., Thrush Press Inc., Times Square Book Bazaar Inc., Charles Tozzo Inc., Thomas Pride Mills Inc., undated (Box 173)
    - Excelsior Window Trimming Corp., I. Posner Inc., Raymond service Inc., Mercury Furniture Corp., undated (Box 174)
    - Gindoff Textile Corp., Automobile Club of New York, Miscellaneous Files of the Legal Dept., Miscellaneous Correspondence of the Legal Dept., undated (Box 175)
  - Subseries IX:C: Records of Local 2110, 1952-1988
    - Macys, Lincoln, Stevens, Minutes Association Committee Leadership-1969, Union Correspondence, Campaign Letters, Leaflets, undated, 1969 (Box 176)
    - National center for the Study of Collective Bargaining, Minutes- Exec. Board, Minutes- Jan 17, 1973, Negotiations-Refusal to Bargain-1975, Negotiations, Pensions, TCEA-Miscellaneous, Job Descriptions, TCMEA, TCEA Strike-1975, TCEA Inception & Negotiation, Unemployment-Students (decision), Reports on Proprietary Schools, Wagner, Live Campaign, undated, 1973, 1975 (Box 177)
    - House Memos, Misc. Assoc. Business, Copies of 1941 Constitution, Harper-List of Accounts, Media Project, Committee on Assoc. Org.-Apr-Jun 1969, Merit & Promotional Increase Research, Elmsford, Dept. of Labor, Grievances, Willie Lane, List of Members-1971, BPI Salary Survey, Correspondence, Arbitrations, Association Library, Contract Proposals-Negotiation Committee, Correspondence to & from Signe-1969, Profit Sharing, Pension Plans, Retirement Plans, Unit Status, AGs Study of Pension Plan-1970, Association-Misc (Bond, etc.), Franklin Square Agency, Grievance Committee, Collective Bargaining Settlements in New York State-Jun 1970, Harpers Magazine & Press, Confidential Employees, AGs Report on Retirement Plan, Apprenticeship-Training, Job Reclassification & Wages-1967, Ed Hewes (confidential), Cost of Living, Confidential, undated, 1967, 1971 (Box 178)
    - General Office & Screen Files: United Artists Corp., Rabinowitz & Boudin, Rudd Plastics Corp., Luigi Serra, Mgt. Literature & Anti Union Employees, S&S&L-ULP, Union Literature, Producers Distributing Agency, The Silent Watchman Corp., Screen-General Correspondence, Loews Inc., Columbia Pictures Corp. Correspondence: 1961-1977, Columbia Pictures Contracts-1952-1968, Columbia Arbitration, undated, 1952-1977 (Box 179)
    - General Office Files: Glemby Co., Horowitz-Margarten, C.Howard Co., International Arts & Sciences Press, Kleinberg Kaplan Wolff & Cohen, London Records Co., Marboro Book, Metropolitan Books, Mutual Real Estate Investment Trust, NY Civil Liberties Union-1971, New World Review Inc., Olinski Charles, undated, 1971 (Box 180)
    - ASCAP, Beth Emeth, Beth Israel, Box One Studio, Cooper Union, ICI, The Museum of Broadcasting, NY Council on Alcoholism, NYIT, MCI, NY Psychotherapy & Counseling, Riverside, Steward Tabori & Chang, Weil Gotshal & Manges, Organization, Trade & Technical Schools, PSI & NYBS, World Hunger Organization, undated (Box 181)
    - Harper & Row Files: Personnel Correspondence, "The Runner", Stewards Meeting Minutes, Leaflets, Survey Material, Ballots, Job Postings, Departmental Memos, Dummy Schedules, Election Materials, undated (Box 182)
    - Harcourt Brace Jovanovich-Misc., Plenum, Merit ULP, St. Martins Press, undated (Box 183)
    - General Office Files: DCA Food Industries Inc., Damon Creations, Direct Mail Envelope, Equity Window Cleaning, Glemby International: Grievance; Negotiations-1988; Carmine Marino Case; Negotiations-1978, undated, 1978, 1988 (Box 184)
    - General Education Files: Barnard College, Board of Global Ministries: Tony Acevedo Grievance; Dolores Smith Griev.; Travel Griev., Crown Business Institute-1985-86, Long Island Historical Society, NYU Organizing Effort, Royal Business School, Sarah Lawrence College, Teachers College-Librarians, Union College, undated, 1985-1986 (Box 185)
    - District 65 Office Files & Correspondence: Constitution (Original & Copies), T.C.I., F.D.C., AAP Material, Union Busting, "Mother Jones" May 1980, House Newsletters, Bella, P-4, "To Be Filed", Affiliation, Anti-Union Moves, Contract: 1975-Originals, Literature: "Association vs. Union"; Dues; Pension Plan; Security Plan, Mailings: Letters from Exec. Board; Agendas & Minutes, undated, 1975, 1980 (Box 186)
    - Misc. Shop Files Including: American Civil Liberties Union, Ames & Rollins, Amsc School Publications, Aspira of New York, Barnard College, Club Med, Columbia University, Daka (Food Services Museum of Mod. Art), DCA, Eisner & Levy, Harper Collins, Maxwell Macmillan-Thompson, Metropolitan News/C&S, Museum of Mod. Art, Monthly Review, National Jewish Hospital, New York Civil Liberties Union, New York Historical Society, Non-Traditional Employment for Women, Prentice Hall, Rabinowitz Boudin, Silent Watchman, Teachers College, Technical Careers Institute, Union Theological Seminary, Unitron Graphics, Viking Penguin Press, Village Voice, Columbia Pictures, Twentieth Century Fox, Warner Bros., Paramount Pictures, undated (Box 187)
  - Subseries IX:D: Files of Frank Brown, 1933-1989
    - Misc. Files: Alliance for Labor Action, AFL-CIO, AFSCME, American Federation of Jewish Fighters, American Jewish Congress, American ORT, Americans for Progressive Israel, American Trade Union Council, American Travel Assoc., American Zionist Committee, Amivest, Anti-Semitism Reports & Articles from Various Org.s, Anti-Union Material, Applicant Class Material, Arbitration Reports, Art Steel, Material on Legal Aid Attorneys, B.N.A. Reports, undated (Box 188)
    - Harper & Row: 1982; Moynihan & Rangel Correspondence; Testimony-Hearing 3/22/84; Decision; Tate, Harvard: Briefs; UAW; Organizing Budget; Medical Area; Personnel, Dental Center, Graphic Arts Guild, Massenberg-Mary Ann, California Trip Info, DSOC Transcription-7/81, Barbara Rahke, Art Steel, undated, 1981-1986 (Box 189)
    - Unorganized Shop Surveys: 6 Portfolios, NLRB Negotiations: 1 Portfolio, undated, 1965 (Box 190)
    - Bureau of Wholesale Sales Representatives, New Jersey Convention- Cherry Hill 9/9-13/1981, New School, Newspaper Clippings, New York State Workmens Compensation, New York Trade Unionists for Labor Israel, National Organization of Legal Service Workers, Material on John Oliva, Organization Material, OSHA Material, Arthur Osman File, Peace Folder, Personnel Matters, PS&T United, Pension Plan Material, undated, Sep 9, 1981-Sep 13, 1981 (Box 191)
    - Carl Shier (Chicago), Inter-Office Memos, Personal Mail (Frank Brown), Frank Browns Team Meeting Records, Frank Brown-Personal Correspondence, Miscellaneous Pictures, Carnegie Hall: King-Osman Affair 5/4/82, Frank Brown Accident File, Organizational Reports (Frank Brown-Zeke Cohen), undated, May 4, 1982 (Box 192)
    - District 65 Shops by Region, TOP Division, Region 9A, UAW Convention 1983, UAW 26th Convention-6/1-6/1986, Meeting Notes: Detroit 5/12/69 Los Angeles 6/15/69, undated, 1969-1986 (Box 193)
    - UAW 27th Const. Conv. Dalla TX 5/15-20/83, Saftey & Health: UAW, United Department Stores, United Farm Workers Org., United Food & Commercial Workers, United Furniture Workers Union, United Housing Foundation, United Jewish Appeal, United Labor Press, United Mine Workers, United Paperworkers International Union, United Syrup & Preserves Employees, Unorganized Targets, Voter Registration Material, War on Poverty/Facts & Figures on Unemployment, Warehouse Production & Sales Employees Union, Ted Weiss, Woolworth Stores, Worker, Workers Defense League, Workmans Circle, World Jewish Congress, Yiddish National Theater, Yivo Institute for Jewish Research, 1972 Convention: Montmarte Hotel Miami Beach FL 4/18-20/72, Strike Assistance Requests, National Council Memos, Strike Benefits Requests, Merger Agreement: R.W.D.S.U., Frank Browns Report:NCDWA-Detroit MI 1970, undated, 1970-1983 (Box 194)
    - Legal Dept. Memos, Liberal Party, Maritime Port Council, Master Truckmen of America, Mayors Commission on Exploitation of Workers, Millinery Workers Union-Joint Board, Minimum Wage Material, Moving Picture Machine Operators-Local 306, National Conferences of Christians & Jews, National Labor Relations Board, National Maritime Union, National Organization of Industrial Trade Unions, NAWACAS Speeches, Bureau of Wholesale Representatives, NAWCAS Conventions: 12/12/81, 12/11-16/79, 12/11-18/80, 7/18-21/81, undated, 1979-1981 (Box 195)
    - AMPAL-American-Israel Corp., Anti-Aparthied Mat'l-6/14/86, Art Steel Inc.-1983-84, Attorneys: Eisner & Levy-1984, 1985; Joe Fine-1984, Assoc. of Legal Aid Attorneys, Bank Hapoalim-1984, Frank Barbaro Material, Ben Berman Contract Info-1983, Black Affairs Committee, Blue Cross Blue Shield, Frank Brown-Trustee, Collier Lending Institutions & the Bancruptcy Code, Christmas List-83/86/87, City of Hope: Robal Chapt.-84, Coalition of Black Trade Unionists, Colt Strike Material, Contract Expirations, Crew Records, 50-Grand Drive, DCA Food Industries, Dist. 65-UAW: Brief History 1933; Education Dept.; Staff Retirement Plan; Unlimited Seniority List 1936-71, Dun & Bradstreet Reports, Eastern Airlines Material Pete Evanoff-Chicago IL, Executive Committee Meeting Memos, Federal Election Commission Letters-1985, undated, 1933-1987 (Box 196)
    - Teamster Lodge 2201-B'nai B'rith, Brandeis University, Bond Archives-Trade Union Council 1959-60, Hugh L. Carey Material, Center for Labor & Industrial Relations, Citizens Advisory Committee-NYC Dept. of Corrections, City Election Material, City Of Hope, Civil Rights-United Steel Workers of America, CLUW, Communication Workers of America, Conference of Presidents of Major American-Jewish Organization, Congressional Record, undated, 1959-1960 (Box 197)
    - Israel Crisis-1969, Israel Housing, Israel Weekly Digest, Jewelry Workers Union, The Jewish Agency, Jewish Currents, Jewish Daily Forward-Jewish Day:Freiheit, Jewish Labor Committee, Jewish National Fund, Jewish Newsletter, Kashruth Supervisors Union, Kayser-Roth Corp., Material on the Kerner Report, Knitgoods Workers Union, Kreiger & Chodash, Labor Action Coalition, Labor Law Reform Material, Labor Theater Material, Labor Zionist Alliance, Labor Reports, Laundry Workers Local 284, Leather Goods, Eisner & Levy, undated, 1969 (Box 198)
    - Other than Dist. 65 Convention Material, Constitution, Cooper Union Labor Institute, Committee of Racial Equality (C.O.R.E.), Corrugated Trade Union Council, Corrugated Locals 300 & 381, Credit Union-Dist. 65, Dental Center Material, Dept. of Labor-State of NY, Dept. Store Locals, Der Wecker, District Attorney-County of Kings, Dist. 65 Special Material, Dist. 65 Localities Nationwide, District Council 37, Educational Staff Material, Electrical Workers Local 3, ERISA Material, Four Freedoms Hotel, Full Employment Material, Fur Workers Joint Board, Garment Center Security Inf., Givat Haviva, Grievance Reports, Harper & Row, HIAS, undated (Box 199)